{"data":[{"question":"Did you see all the apples _____ that tree?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"John lives _____ 357 North Highland Drive.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"The expiration date is printed _____ the bottom of the box.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Please put more potatoes _____ my plate.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"It gets very cold _____ the desert at night.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+  in: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ at: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ on: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Mr. and Mrs. Barton live _____ Oak Street.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Use on with street name","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Did you put your clothes _____ the closet?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Have you ever ridden _____ a donkey?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Look at all those cows _____ that field!","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Mr. Thompson isn't here right now. He's _____ the bank.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"}]}